Guide to the J.G. Link and Company Records 1939-1965
Montana State University-Bozeman Library
- Project Files, 1939-1965; Series 4
  - Valley County Courthouse – Working Drawing Files - #4 (Box-folder 22/17)
  - V.F.W. – Club (Box-folder 23/1)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission – Glendive, Montana – Shop Drawings (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commission – Miles City, Montana – Shop Drawings (Box-folder 23/3)
  - Wagner Heating and Plumbing – Valley County Courthouse, 1972 (Box-folder 23/4)
  - Weissman Residence (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Wheatland Memorial Hospital – Shop Drawings (Box-folder 23/6)
  - W.H. George Co. Mortuary – Great Falls, Montana, 1958 (Box-folder 23/7)
    [1344; 141]